So far we've been talking about cuisine and simple actions that we may need to do when we're going to
到目前为止，我们一直在谈论美食和我们可能需要做的简单动作。
describe how to cook something.
描述如何做饭。
Now we're going to continue with a few common phrases that we can use as we're describing the process
现在我们将继续使用一些常用短语，我们可以在描述过程时使用它们
of cooking before we actually get into an example recipe.
在我们真正进入示例食谱之前进行烹饪。
OK.
好的。
Batter it in breadcrumbs.
把它裹在面包屑里。
Now batter can be a verb or a noun but it means to completely cover something in what's called batter
现在击球手可以是动词或名词，但它意味着完全覆盖所谓击球手的东西
batter batter is a mix of different different ingredients.
面糊面糊是不同不同成分的混合物。
So batter it in bread crumbs.
所以把它裹在面包屑里。
So we're going to basically roll it around in the bread crumbs cook on low heat for 20 minutes.
所以我们基本上要把它在面包屑里滚来滚去，用小火煮20分钟。
So we often need to describe how hot the if we're using a burner for using a burner.
所以我们经常需要描述如果我们使用燃烧器来使用燃烧器有多热。
How hot that is.
那是多么的热。
We have low heat and I think you can probably guess we have then medium heat And we have high heat cook
我们有低热量，我想你可能会猜到我们有中等热量而且我们有高温厨师
on high heat cook on low heat cook on medium heat And then we can say how long we should do that.
大火煮 小火煮 中火煮 然后我们可以说我们应该做多长时间。
OK.
好的。
But sometimes we don't know how long exactly that will take.
但有时我们不知道这需要多长时间。
We don't know if it's 20 minutes.
我们不知道是不是20分钟。
Right.
正确的。
So instead of saying how many minutes to cook it describe the condition.
因此，与其说要煮多少分钟，不如说是描述了情况。
Describe what it should look like before you do something else cook until golden brown golden brown
描述在你做其他东西之前它应该是什么样子，直到变成金棕色 金棕色
that's the color of it.
这就是它的颜色。
So once it becomes golden brown then do the next thing add the lettuce or whatever else you need to
所以一旦它变成金黄色，接下来就加入生菜或其他你需要的东西
do cook it until it's golden brown.
把它煮到金黄色。
OK.
好的。
Stir fry the onions and slowly add the sauce now to stir fry as an action is to move the food around
翻炒洋葱，现在慢慢加入酱汁翻炒，因为动作是移动食物
in a pan or a walk.
在平底锅或散步。
As we talked about a walk is generally what we used to cook Chinese food.
正如我们所说的散步一般是我们用来做中国菜的。
OK.
好的。
And then slowly as we're doing this we're adding another thing or adding sauce or adding sauce.
然后慢慢地，当我们这样做时，我们正在添加另一种东西或添加酱汁或添加酱汁。
So we're doing this and another action at the same time.
所以我们同时做这个和另一个动作。
So when you need to describe two actions at the same time do it like this.
因此，当您需要同时描述两个动作时，请这样做。
Do this action right.
正确执行此操作。
Boil it and then slowly add or whatever you need to say that you need to do at the same time steam it
煮沸，然后慢慢加入，或者你需要说的任何东西，同时蒸它
for 15 minutes and let it cool let it cool.
15分钟，让它冷却让它冷却。
That's pretty straightforward.
这很简单。
It's saying two actions in a row you're not doing those two at the same time.
这是说连续两个动作你不是同时做这两个动作。
First you steam it with a steamer for example.
例如，首先你用蒸锅蒸。
Then you turn off the heat and then you leave it.
然后你关掉暖气，然后离开它。
You don't touch it for 15 minutes then maybe you can eat it or maybe you do the next step.
你不碰它 15 分钟然后也许你可以吃它或者你可以做下一步。
OK then we have these three phrases which can allow us to basically describe a next action.
好的，那么我们有了这三个短语，它们可以让我们基本上描述下一个动作。
Next you need to for example.
接下来你需要例如。
Next you need to stir fry the onions and slowly add the sauce whatever the next action is.
接下来，您需要翻炒洋葱并慢慢加入酱汁，无论下一步是什么。
It's a way to sort of move on to the next thing.
这是一种进入下一件事的方式。
Once that's done make sure to.
一旦完成，请确保。
So as a reminder when we're describing a specific step we can say this one once that's done steam it
所以提醒一下，当我们描述一个特定的步骤时，我们可以在完成后说这个
for 15 minutes and let it cool once that's done.
15分钟，完成后让它冷却。
Make sure to pour a little bit of soy sauce on top or whatever it is.
确保在上面倒一点酱油或任何东西。
OK.
好的。
When it's finished now maybe we could talk about a specific step here or the whole thing when it's finished.
现在完成后，也许我们可以在这里讨论一个特定的步骤或完成后的整个事情。
Serve it in a bowl or when it's finished.
将其放入碗中或完成后食用。
Add a little bit of sugar on top.
在上面加一点糖。
Or we could say sprinkle.
或者我们可以说洒。
We have all kinds of little words like this that you can learn separately because there are so many
我们有各种这样的小词，你可以单独学习，因为有很多
of them sprinkling is basically adding a powder salt or sugar or something like that to the top of something
其中洒水基本上是在顶部添加粉末盐或糖或类似的东西东西
grains of something or a powder of something to the top to sprinkle with your fingers.
用手指撒在上面的东西颗粒或粉末。
We also use for example pinch a pinch is when you grab something with these two fingers a pinch of for
我们还使用例如捏捏是当你用这两个手指抓东西的时候捏捏
example a pinch of salt a pinch of sugar when it's finished sprinkle a few pinches of salt on top and
例如，一小撮盐，一撮糖，完成后在上面撒上几撮盐，然后
serve it in a large serving bowl.
把它放在一个大碗里。
OK so that's pretty simple.
好的，这很简单。
These are some common phrases certainly not all the phrases that we could possibly talk about or use
这些是一些常见的短语，当然不是我们可以谈论或使用的所有短语
but some of the common phrases that we will come across when we need to describe the process of cooking
但是当我们需要描述烹饪过程时，我们会遇到一些常见的短语
a dish.
一道菜。